{
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "What was the first movie in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
      "option1": "The Avengers",
      "option2": "Iron Man",
      "option3": "Thor",
      "option4": "Spider-Man",
      "correctAnswer": "Iron Man"
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "Which of these actors DID NOT appear in Pulp Fiction?",
      "option1": "Samuel L Jackson",
      "option2": "John Turturro",
      "option3": "Bruce Willis",
      "option4": "Uma Thurman",
      "correctAnswer": "John Turturro"
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "What is it called when an actor breaks character to directly address the audience?",
      "option1": "Bending the narrative",
      "option2": "Sweeping the rug",
      "option3": "Breaking the 4th wall",
      "option4": "Following the loose thread",
      "correctAnswer": "Breaking the 4th wall"
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "Which of these movies was NOT directed by M. Night Shyamalan?",
      "option1": "The Sixth Sense",
      "option2": "Signs",
      "option3": "Glass",
      "option4": "The Ring",
      "correctAnswer": "The Ring"
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "Which  of the following is filmmaker Michael Bay known for?",
      "option1": "Explosions",
      "option2": "Fanciful costume design",
      "option3": "Sweeping Western lanscape",
      "option4": "Romantic comedy",
      "correctAnswer": "Explosions"
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "In the movie 'Frozen', who was Olaf?",
      "option1": "A ghost",
      "option2": "A snowman",
      "option3": "A reindeer",
      "option4": "A knight",
      "correctAnswer": "A snowman"
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "Who directed Dil Chahta Hai?",
      "option1": "Zoya Akhtar",
      "option2": "Aamir Khan",
      "option3": "Farhan Akhtar",
      "option4": "Reema Kagti",
      "correctAnswer": "Farhan Akhtar"
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "Fow which of these movies did Leonardo DiCaprio win an Oscar for Best Actor?",
      "option1": "The Revenant",
      "option2": "The Last King of Scotland",
      "option3": "Blood Diamond",
      "option4": "Titanic",
      "correctAnswer": "The Revenant"
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "In the 'Godfather' series, where qas Vito Corleone born?",
      "option1": "Rome",
      "option2": "New York City",
      "option3": "Corleone, Sicilly",
      "option4": "Athens",
      "correctAnswer": "Corleone, Sicilly"
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "Which is the only movie to win 13 Filmfare Awards?",
      "option1": "Uri: The Surgical Strike",
      "option2": "Article 15",
      "option3": "Saand Ki Aankh",
      "option4": "Gully Boy",
      "correctAnswer": "Gully Boy"
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "question": "Who is the director of Baahubali",
      "option1": "V.V. Vinayak",
      "option2": "S.S. Rajamouli",
      "option3": "Koratala Siva",
      "option4": "Shankar",
      "correctAnswer": "S.S. Rajamouli"
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "question": "Who among the following made first Film Theatre of India?",
      "option1": "Lumiere Brothers",
      "option2": "Mani Sethna",
      "option3": "Dada Saheb Phalke",
      "option4": "Dhirendra Nath Ganguly",
      "correctAnswer": "Mani Sethna"
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "question": "Which of the following regional cinema referred to as Kollywood?",
      "option1": "Punjabi Cinema",
      "option2": "Tamil Cinema",
      "option3": "Telugu Cinema",
      "option4": "Bengali Cinema",
      "correctAnswer": "Tamil Cinema"
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "question": "What is the name of the National-award winning Bollywood choreographer, who recently passed away?",
      "option1": "Saroj Khan",
      "option2": "Protik Prakash",
      "option3": "Tridib Ghosh",
      "option4": "Geetha Nagabhushan",
      "correctAnswer": "Saroj Khan"
    },
    {
      "number": 15,
      "question": "The Versatile Bollywood actor Irrfan Khan, who recently passed away, had won National award for which movie?",
      "option1": "Life Of Pi",
      "option2": "The Lunchbox",
      "option3": "Paan Singh Tomar",
      "option4": "Hindi Medium",
      "correctAnswer": "Paan Singh Tomar"
    },
    {
      "number": 16,
      "question": "Which movie has become the first Bollywood film to go plastic-free?",
      "option1": "War",
      "option2": "Coolie No 1",
      "option3": "Mission Mangal",
      "option4": "Gully Boy",
      "correctAnswer": "Coolie No 1"
    },
    {
      "number": 17,
      "question": "Which among these movies are directed by zoya akthar?",
      "option1": "Zindagi Na Milegi Dobara",
      "option2": "Yeh Jawani Hai Deewani",
      "option3": "Mission Mangal",
      "option4": "War",
      "correctAnswer": "Zindagi Na Milegi Dobara"
    },
    {
      "number": 18,
      "question": "Which Bollywood personality has been honoured by European Union for strengthening Europe-India cultural ties?",
      "option1": "Hrithik Roshan",
      "option2": "Amitabh Bachchan",
      "option3": "Ranveer Singh",
      "option4": "Akshay Kumar",
      "correctAnswer": "Amitabh Bachchan"
    },
    {
      "number": 19,
      "question": "Who was the music director of roja?",
      "option1": "A.R. Rahman",
      "option2": "Ilayaraja",
      "option3": "S.P. Balasubramanian",
      "option4": "S.V Venkatraman",
      "correctAnswer": "A.R. Rahman"
    },
    {
      "number": 20,
      "question": "Which Indian bollywood personality has been honoured with the 2017 Parmod Mahajan Smriti Award?",
      "option1": "Amitabh Bachchan",
      "option2": "Shatrughan Sinha",
      "option3": "Sharmila Tagore",
      "option4": "Anupam Kher",
      "correctAnswer": "Anupam Kher"
    },
    {
      "number": 21,
      "question": "Which of these south Indian song is sung by Farhan Akthar",
      "option1": "The Break Up song",
      "option2": "I Don't Know",
      "option3": "Bharat ane nenu",
      "option4": "My love is gone",
      "correctAnswer": "I Don't Know"
    },
    {
      "number": 22,
      "question": "Which of these south Indian song is sung by Farhan Akthar",
      "option1": "The Break Up song",
      "option2": "I Don't Know",
      "option3": "Bharat ane nenu",
      "option4": "My love is gone",
      "correctAnswer": "I Don't Know"
    },
    {
      "number": 22,
      "question": "Who was the lead actor in the movie M.S.Dhoni: The Untold Story?",
      "option1": "Sushanth Singh Rajput",
      "option2": "Akshay Kumar",
      "option3": "Ranveer Singh",
      "option4": "Ayushmann Khurrana",
      "correctAnswer": "Sushanth Singh Rajput"
    },
    {
      "number": 23,
      "question": "Who was the lead actor in the movie M.S.Dhoni: The Untold Story?",
      "option1": "Sushanth Singh Rajput",
      "option2": "Akshay Kumar",
      "option3": "Ranveer Singh",
      "option4": "Ayushmann Khurrana",
      "correctAnswer": "Sushanth Singh Rajput"
    },
    {
      "number": 24,
      "question": "What's the highest rated movie on imdb?",
      "option1": "The Shawshank Redemption",
      "option2": "The Godfather",
      "option3": "Inception",
      "option4": "Interstellar",
      "correctAnswer": "The Shawshank Redemption"
    },
    {
      "number": 25,
      "question": "Which among these movies are not directed by Christopher Nolan?",
      "option1": "Tenet",
      "option2": "The Godfather",
      "option3": "Inception",
      "option4": "Interstellar",
      "correctAnswer": "The Godfather"
    }
  ]
  }
  